You are welcome to Funny Madness.  This Is Where
You See The World News Funny Videos.  Please don't
forget to like, share and
subscribe.  Thank you.
Three to one.
[laughter]
oh
morning sleep
[laughter]
depression [laughter]
I [laughter]
very low
[laughter]
God [sudden heavy breathing]
[screaming sound] [laughter] [laughter]
Sawans [laughter]
[laughter] take it take it
[laughter] [laughter]
six garbage
left [laughter
]
ho [laughter]
[laughter]
what is happening here brother
what is happening here brother where is he stuck
what is happening what has happened
so
[laughter]
hello
start
baba re baba bastard bastard
bastard
brother
[laughter]
[music] I will
not let you touch my long black hair Raja.
Yes brother, tell me how should I cut my hair?
How can I cut it like this?  You know he's been
cutting hair for 10 years.  [MUSIC]
A Few Moments Later.
Come on brother, it's done.
[laughter]
How about that
?
[laughter]
Hello madam, look ahead and
leave the mobile, otherwise you will fall on your face
[music]
no
Begum, just enough, just
by God
[laughter]
[music]
[laughter] I have made a
big mistake, sir.
[laughter]
What will happen?
[screaming]
[laughter]
This